So the way I see it is there's the magic of the earth and there's the magic of the mind.
And it bothers me when I see black folks thinking that the mention of witches is a bad thing because the folks that sold you that as like a thought process, they literally eradicated witches so that they could do the dark magic of the mind on you.
They are doing the manipulation. They are doing the brainwashing. They are taking the powerful herbal aspects of the earth and turning them into narcotics that disconnect you from the earth.
Witches exist in many forms and essentially were the folks who knew and understood the earth and its plants and its magnetism, etc. to heal.
And they were connected intrinsically to that and therefore able to point out that this is valuable and something we should protect.
The folks that were burning them at stakes, etc. are the ones who tricked you and told you that the earth is actually not important.
Your God is in the sky. Don't worry about down here and have successfully for the past hundreds of years reaped and sold the benefits of that earth while genociding those who lived off of it and while continuously keeping conflict in the places of those who are supposed to be owning it.
Hence Africa. Hence Africa. So when we talk about the concept of witching, witchy witchery is just literally knowing and understanding the ways beyond what you're being told.
It's what you're being. It's what you're being. It's what you feel and what you understand about the earth that you come from.
Witching is having a connectivity, right? And an intuition that is attached to spirit.
These are all things that humans was like casually doing until a certain brand of human came in and was like, actually, we need to cut that out because we're trying to come up.
And they want to come up on darkness. Like they're sadists. Their power is derived from death and destruction. Witches power is derived from life and growth.
It's not to say that you can't do dark magic, but to consider that all witching is dark magic would assume that all humans are about the darkness and we're all not.
So just something to think about as you're considering witching. You need to watch this video again because I know you didn't get it all the first time.
He began to support the labor unions. He questioned government allocation of resources.
He advocated for reparations. Where are we cutting the check?
It was after all of this, when he had evolved into Martin Luther, the king, that this nation thought to be rid of him.